701panduan.com 2010-04-22

# 701Panduan- Disclaimer

**DISCLAIMER**

701Panduan Sdn Bhd kindly reminds that you read carefully and fully understand this disclaimer before using 701Panduan.com for searching lifestyle and business information. The policy will govern your use of 701panduan.com.

“You” and “User” refer to User’s use of 701Panduan.com represents his/her consent of all the contents in this DISCLAIMER. “The Company” refers to Advertiser or Dealer Information.

(1)  Considering that 701Panduan.com displays business information automatically in a non-human-indexed manner according to the keywords entered by the user, 701Panduan Sdn Bhd shall not take any responsibility, or undertake any liability, warranties for all but not limited to incidents, negligence, infringement, and subsequent losses (including infection of computer viruses due to linking to other websites) due to use of 701Panduan.com.

(2)  The truthfulness and legality of company information, business information or product information from the use of 701Panduan shall be solely guaranteed by The Company and is not relevant to 701Panduan in any way, nor shall 701Panduan be held liable for that.

(3)  You shall bear all risks for using the search result. 701Panduan Sdn Bhd makes no warranty, in any form, that the search result can meet the demands of the user, that the search service will not be interrupted, that the search result is secure, error-free, prompt or legal. 701Panduan Sdn Bhd shall not be held legally responsible in any way for failure in using 701Panduan.com caused by any reasons, including but not limit to faults in network traffic or communication lines.

(4)  In case that any entity or person believes that the contents that can be searched through 701Panduan.com may infringe upon its right to information network dissemination, they shall directly contact the specific Company or Dealer for resolution. The liability shall be solely borne by the Company or Dealer. It shall not be related to, or borne by 701Panduan Sdn Bhd.

(5)  The website may be conflicting with some software installed on the user’s computer systems. 701Panduan Sdn Bhd shall not take any responsibility for interest losses thus incurred. Any material downloaded or otherwise obtained though the use of the service is done at your own discretion and risk. You will be solely responsible to for any damage to your computer and loss of data due to the downloaded material.

(6)  701Panduan shall not be held responsible for any losses, whether direct, indirect, or consequential, in computer hardware, software damages, or information exposures, etc, arising from use or nonuse of the service provided by 701Panduan.

(7)  You shall be solely responsible for any infringement of the third party interest in information provided to 701Panduan by uploading, communicating, entering or any other manners.

701Panduan Sdn Bhd reserves the rights to change its terms and conditions of Service from time to time as deem necessary at its sole discretion.

**The Information We Collect**

We may use your information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout and service. When you submit business information, your information will not be disclosed to third party without your consent. We do not sell, trade or exchange any personally information of our Users. We may use information to execute marketing campaign from time to time. You will be given opportunity to opt out from any marketing and communications with 701Panduan Sdn Bhd.

PRIVACY POLICY

[701Panduan Sdn Bhd ](http://www.701panduan.com/)(“701Panduan”) collects information from users for a number of reasons.

Please read carefully our policy below on data collection and use of the data collected. This policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and/or operated by 701Panduan. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various sites or services and assume no responsibility for their content or privacy policies. A link from our site to another site does not imply endorsement of that site.

We may amend this policy from time to time, and we will post any such amended policies on this page. The amended policy will be effective immediately upon posting and will apply to all data that we have previously collected _or data that we store or process on an ongoing basis_.

_**When is information collected from you?**_

  * When you register for any of [701Panduan](http://www.701panduan.com/)'s services on websites owned and/or operated by [701Panduan](http://www.701panduan.com/), when you take part in any contest, survey or promotion conducted by [701Panduan](http://www.701panduan.com/) and/or its business partners and/or when you register as a member of websites hosted by [701Panduan](http://www.701panduan.com/) on behalf of its business partners or use services on such websites, we may ask you for personal information (including, without limitation, your name, email address, account password, gender, phone number, physical address, occupation, preferences, photos, etc.). We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other [701Panduan](http://www.701panduan.com/) services, or publicly available information.
  * We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to 701Panduan in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.
  * When you visit [701Panduan](http://www.701panduan.com/)’s websites, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
  * We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed.

_**What is the information used for?**_

  * To provide goods and services by [701Panduan](http://www.701panduan.com/) or its designated representatives and/or business partners to you or parties designated by you and matters ancillary thereto.
  * To verify and process payment when you purchase goods and services from our sites.
  * For verification and record of your personal particulars, including comparing it with information from other sources, and using the information to communicate with you.
  * To conduct statistical analysis of the users of our sites, including the number of users, the frequency of use, profile of users, and using such analysis for our business plans, the enhancement of our products and services, targeted advertisements and conveying such information in broad terms (but not information in relation to specific individuals) to third parties who have or propose to have business dealings with us.
  * To send you information, promotions and updates including marketing and advertising materials in relation to our goods and services and those of third party organizations selected by us.
  * To comply with any order of court or directive from authorities investigating any alleged offence, misdeeds and/or abuse or for the purposes of taking legal action against any users for breach of the Terms of Use.
  * For the above purposes by third parties (who may be based outside Malaysia) who offer goods and services or sponsor contests or other promotional programs on our sites, whether in conjunction with us or not, if you purchase such goods, use such services or participate in such contests and promotional programs.

_**Will your personal information be shared with anyone?**_

As a general rule, we do not disclose specific information about our users to any third parties, save for the purposes set out above. However, in the event that:

  * you participate in contests or other promotional programs on our site sponsored or organized by third parties;
  * you purchase goods and services offered by third parties or offer goods and services to third parties on our sites;
  * you give us your permission or consent to do so; or
  * the information in question is publicly-available information,

your information may be disclosed to and used by such third parties. Although we are committed to safeguarding your privacy, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you submit to us, or to or from our sites or services.

_**Can you change and update your particulars?**_

We encourage you to change or update your particulars, if the same are inaccurate or not updated, and you may do so at Information Updates  page.

_**How your data is protected**_

[701Panduan](http://www.701panduan.com/) will take commercially reasonable steps to ensure that personal data are protected from unauthorised access.

Access to your data is password protected. Thus, no other party, including employees of 701Panduan, can change the information. However, you must remember to log off from your account and close the browser window and clear your cache after use so that no unauthorised party can have access. You must not, at any time, divulge your password to any third party.

All information gathered by 701Panduan is stored in systems that may only be accessed by authorised staff of 701Panduan Sdn Bhd using assigned user ids and passwords.
